Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[Reborn from the Ashes]
[الولادة من الرماد]
[Episode 22]
[الحلقة 22]
Wen Yueqian, you're courting death.
وين يويه تشيان، أنت تغازل الموت.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
if I could beat you once,
لو استطعت أن أهزمك مرة واحدة،
I can do it again.
أستطيع فعلها مرة أخرى.
I won't let you off.
لن أتركك تفلت من العقاب.
Then let's wait and see.
فلننتظر ونرى.
Father, now Su Guang is dead,
أبي، لقد مات سو غوانغ الآن.
and the account book is gone.
واختفى دفتر الحسابات.
How can I seek justice for you?
كيف يمكنني أن أسعى لتحقيق العدالة لك؟
Why are you drinking alone?
لماذا تشرب وحدك؟
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Tonight, only I keep you company.
الليلة، أنا فقط من سيرافقك.
Shouldn't you pour me a drink?
ألا يجب أن تصب لي مشروباً؟
As your sister-in-law, I have to keep our distance.
بصفتي زوجة أخيك، عليّ أن أحافظ على مسافة بيننا.
You didn't know that?
ألم تكن تعلم ذلك؟
I came to bring you some pastries.
جئت لأحضر لكم بعض المعجنات.
I don't want your things.
لا أريد أغراضك.
I have the pastries my husband gave me.
لديّ المعجنات التي أهداني إياها زوجي.
You're drunk. Let's head back.
أنت ثمل. لنعد أدراجنا.
In the middle of the night instead of sleeping,
في منتصف الليل بدلاً من النوم،
why are you bothering my wife?
لماذا تزعج زوجتي؟
She was drinking alone at night.
كانت تشرب بمفردها في الليل.
I just saw she was lonely,
لقد رأيت للتو أنها كانت تشعر بالوحدة،
so I came to keep her company.
لذا جئت لأؤنسها.
Young Master Qi, someone's here to pick me up.
يا سيد تشي الشاب، هناك من سيأتي ليأخذني.
Well played, Wen Yueqian.
أحسنت يا وين يويتشيان.
You actually drank with Wanyan Qi.
لقد شربت بالفعل مع وانيان تشي.
What do you take me for?
ماذا تظنني؟
Jin.
إحساس.
Give me a smile.
ابتسم لي.
Jin,
إحساس،
you're not really angry, are you?
أنت لست غاضباً حقاً، أليس كذلك؟
You drank alone in the middle of the night.
شربتَ وحدك في منتصف الليل.
Afraid I would worry enough about you?
أخشى أن أقلق عليك بما فيه الكفاية؟
So you were worried about me.
إذن كنت قلقاً عليّ.
Then you can tell me directly.
ثم يمكنك إخباري مباشرة.
Why beat around the bush?
لماذا نلف وندور؟
You're drunk.
أنت ثمل.
I'm not drunk.
أنا لست ثملاً.
Smell me.
شمني.
I'm your husband.
أنا زوجك.
If you want to drink,
إذا كنت ترغب في الشرب،
I can keep you company.
يمكنني أن أؤنسك.
You are really nice.
أنت لطيف حقاً.
Qingran,
كينغران،
go home first and sober up.
اذهب إلى المنزل أولاً واستعد وعيك.
♪Melt the snow on my shoulders♪
♪أذيب الثلج على كتفي♪
♪Yet I can't fully express my longing for you♪
♪لكنني لا أستطيع التعبير بشكل كامل عن شوقي إليك♪
♪Holding a fallen flower petal♪
♪أمسك بتلة زهرة ساقطة♪
♪Not in vain is the destined calamity♪
♪ليست المصيبة المقدرة عبثاً♪
♪Torturing every drop of blood♪
♪تعذيب كل قطرة دم♪
Xiao Jin,
شياو جين,
you don't follow the rules.
أنت لا تلتزم بالقواعد.
Who was holding my arm last night, refusing to let go?
من كان يمسك بذراعي الليلة الماضية، ويرفض تركها؟
Wen Yueqian,
ون يويه تشيان,
you must have forgotten.
لا بد أنك نسيت.
You're now my wife.
أنتِ زوجتي الآن.
Whether I become your wife depends on my choice.
إن أصبحت زوجتك أم لا يعتمد على اختياري.
Why have you brought me here?
لماذا أحضرتني إلى هنا؟
Brought you?
أحضرتك؟
That word sounds so harsh.
تبدو تلك الكلمة قاسية للغاية.
I'm only trying to warn you,
أنا فقط أحاول تحذيرك،
the lady you serve is not the real Su Qingran.
السيدة التي تخدمها ليست سو تشينغران الحقيقية.
She's an impostor.
إنها دجالة.
I'm the real lady of the Su Family.
أنا السيدة الحقيقية لعائلة سو.
You should be loyal to me.
يجب أن تكون مخلصاً لي.
If you follow me,
إذا كنت تتابعني،
I promise you'll enjoy endless wealth and honor.
أعدك بأنك ستنعم بثروة وشرف لا حدود لهما.
Don't think that just because you have His Highness's favor now,
لا تظن أن مجرد حصولك على رضا سموه الآن يعني أنك ستحظى بالتقدير.
you can look down on Lady Qingran.
يمكنك أن تنظر بازدراء إلى السيدة تشينغران.
You
أنت
aren't worthy.
لا يستحقون ذلك.
I advise you to think carefully.
أنصحك بالتفكير ملياً.
After all, she's just a fake.
فهي في النهاية مجرد مزيفة.
The day I expose her will be her end.
اليوم الذي أكشف فيه أمرها سيكون نهايتها.
As a servant,
كخادم،
you need to choose wisely.
عليك أن تختار بحكمة.
Pick the right tree to rest under.
اختر الشجرة المناسبة لتستريح تحتها.
Go on and chase your Fool's Dream.
انطلق وابحث عن حلمك الأحمق.
From your reaction,
من رد فعلك،
you already knew she was a fake.
كنت تعلم بالفعل أنها مزيفة.
Since that's the case,
وبما أن الأمر كذلك،
why not team up with me?
لماذا لا تنضم إليّ؟
Let's expose her together.
فلنفضحها معاً.
What do you say?
ما رأيك؟
Are you out of your mind?
هل فقدت عقلك؟
Hold her down for me.
أمسكها من أجلي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Even if you kill me,
حتى لو قتلتني،
I will never betray Lady Qingran.
لن أخون السيدة تشينغران أبداً.
What a loyal servant!
يا له من خادم وفي!
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'm not willing to kill you.
أنا لست مستعداً لقتلك.
I'll take my time tormenting you.
سأستغرق وقتي في تعذيبك.
♪Not quite fate, but a shallow bond♪
♪ليس قدراً تماماً، بل رابطة سطحية♪
♪How can this be a loss?♪
♪كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا خسارة؟♪
♪Isn't it just one heart♪
♪أليس هذا مجرد قلب واحد؟♪
♪Split into two sides♪
♪انقسم إلى جانبين♪
♪When love can no longer connect us♪
♪عندما لا يعود الحب قادراً على ربطنا♪
♪This life holds no answers♪
♪لا تحمل هذه الحياة إجابات♪
♪How to achieve three lifetimes without resentment♪
♪كيفية تحقيق ثلاثة أعمار دون ضغينة♪
♪Or regrets♪
♪أو الندم♪
Cuihua.
كويهوا.
Wang Cuihua.
وانغ كويهوا.
Wake up, Cuihua.
استيقظ يا كويهوا.
Lady Qingran...
السيدة قيران...
It was Su Feiyi who did this to you.
كانت سو فايي هي من فعلت هذا بك.
I will go and kill her right now.
سأذهب وأقتلها الآن.
My Lady,
سيدتي،
don't...
لا...
Su Feiyi
سو فيي
has set a trap,
لقد نصب فخاً،
waiting for you.
في انتظاركم.
Cuihua, hold on. Hold on.
كويهوا، تمسكي. تمسكي.
I won't let this go.
لن أدع هذا يمر مرور الكرام.
I'll go get the physician.
سأذهب لأحضر الطبيب.
Physician!
طبيب!
My Lady,
سيدتي،
don't waste your efforts on me.
لا تضيع جهودك عليّ.
Su Feiyi
سو فيي
knows your real identity.
يعرف هويتك الحقيقية.
She intends to harm you.
إنها تنوي إيذاءك.
You must be very careful.
يجب أن تكون حذراً للغاية.
You...
أنت...
When did you find out
متى علمت بذلك؟
about my real identity?
عن هويتي الحقيقية؟
All these years,
طوال هذه السنوات،
no one ever treated me like a person.
لم يعاملني أحد قط كإنسان.
Only you...
أنت فقط...
Only you have cared for me.
أنت وحدك من اهتم بي.
Keep this with you.
احتفظ بهذا معك.
My Lady...
سيدتي...
My Lady, please don't...
سيدتي، أرجوكِ لا...
Cuihua.
كويهوا.
Cuihua, hold on!
كويهوا، انتظر!
I will definitely cure you.
سأشفيك بالتأكيد.
The physician will be here soon.
سيصل الطبيب قريباً.
My Lady,
سيدتي،
it hurts so much.
إنه مؤلم للغاية.
♪Returning to the land as the tide recedes♪
♪العودة إلى اليابسة مع انحسار المد♪
♪Like a fallen leaf drifting away♪
♪مثل ورقة شجر ساقطة تبتعد♪
In my heart,
في قلبي،
you...
أنت...
You have always been Lady Qingran.
لطالما كنتِ السيدة تشينغران.
I hope that in the next life,
أتمنى أن يكون الأمر كذلك في الحياة الأخرى،
I can still serve you.
لا يزال بإمكاني خدمتك.
I, Wang Cuihua,
أنا وانغ كويهوا،
swear to protect you
أقسم على حمايتك
till my last breath.
حتى آخر أنفاسي.
♪The sky becomes my wedding gown♪
♪السماء تصبح فستان زفافي♪
Wang Cuihua!
وانغ كويهوا!
♪I turn into clouds♪
♪أتحول إلى غيوم♪
How could I finish all this food by myself?
كيف لي أن أنهي كل هذا الطعام بمفردي؟
Cuihua, how about
كويهوا، ماذا عن
you sit down and eat with me?
هل تجلس وتتناول الطعام معي؟
Eat more.
تناول المزيد من الطعام.
These are knee guards.
هذه واقيات للركبة.
Remember to wear them properly from now on.
تذكر أن ترتديها بشكل صحيح من الآن فصاعدًا.
Thank you, My Lady.
شكراً لكِ يا سيدتي.
No need to thank me.
لا داعي لشكرني.
Do you like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Thank you, My Lady.
شكراً لكِ يا سيدتي.
If you ever need anything, just tell me.
إذا احتجت إلى أي شيء في أي وقت، فأخبرني فقط.
Cuihua...
كويهوا...
Here, it's all for you.
هنا، كل شيء مُعدّ لك.
Thank you, My Lady.
شكراً لكِ يا سيدتي.
Su Feiyi.
سو فيي.
♪In this world, who exactly♪
♪في هذا العالم، من بالضبط♪
♪Pushed me into the abyss?♪
♪دفعني إلى الهاوية؟♪
♪The sky is silent, and the sea says nothing♪
السماء صامتة، والبحر لا ينطق بكلمة.
♪Who shows me mercy in this world?♪
من يرحمني في هذا العالم؟
♪Cold winds sweep across the wasteland♪
♪ تهبّ رياح باردة على الأرض القاحلة ♪
♪Mercilessly gifting me snow and frost♪
♪يمنحني بلا رحمة الثلج والصقيع♪
♪In this fleeting life♪
♪في هذه الحياة الزائلة♪
♪No mercy, no answers♪
♪لا رحمة، لا إجابات♪
♪Yet one lamp shines, unafraid to go out♪
♪ومع ذلك، لا يزال مصباح واحد يضيء، غير خائف من الانطفاء♪
♪Time can twist, but people aren't perfect♪
قد يتغير الزمن، لكن البشر ليسوا كاملين.
♪Who decides who comes and who parts?♪
♪من يقرر من يأتي ومن يرحل؟♪
♪It all rests on a single hopeful thought♪
♪كل شيء يعتمد على فكرة واحدة تبعث على الأمل♪
♪Why fear one last breath?♪
♪لماذا نخشى اللحظة الأخيرة؟♪
♪Love is brief, full of regrets♪
♪الحب قصير، مليء بالندم♪
♪I paint the sky as a fan♪
أرسم السماء كالمروحة
♪To blow away nightmares and scatter the dust♪
♪لإزالة الكوابيس وتبديد الغبار♪
♪Can't resist the fate of being separated♪
لا أستطيع مقاومة مصير الفراق.
♪By distance♪
♪عن طريق المسافة♪
[Exclusive content rights reserved]
[جميع الحقوق محفوظة]
[by Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[من شركة Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]